Guide to the Cornell University Library Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections records, 1992-2015.
Cornell University Library Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections records, 1992-2015.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University Library Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections records, 1992-2015.
13-6-2691
Cornell University Library Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections.
69 cubic ft.
Records, guest books, video tour, card files, financial records, and correspondence.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Records, files, and miscellany relating to the Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The Division was formed in 1992 with the combination of the Department of Rare Books, the Department of Manuscripts and University Archives, the History of Science Collections, and the Icelandic Collection.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Administrative records of the Division; also book truck labels fancifully annotated by student employees during the transfer of collections from Olin Library to Kroch Library, and guest books signed by early visitors and patrons, August through November, 1992; a video tour of the Division created by Nancy Dean. Icelandic Collection circulation and other card files; records of the Division's Strategic Plan, 1993-94; financial records of the Division; chronological file of outgoing correspondence; magneto-optical disk (MOD) backups; and Division exhibit items, records, and related material. Records compiled by Cheryl Stadel-Bevans, 1998-1999 for an 18-month NHPRC (National Historical Publications and Records Commission)-sponsored project to investigate the requirements for electronic administrative records at Cornell, and a report by Nancy McGovern on electronic student records systems, 2000. Files relating to the John Nolen Research Fund, 1990-2001.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University. Library. Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections.; Dean, Nancy L.; McGovern, Nancy.; Stadel-Bevans, Cheryl.; Cornell University--Libraries.
Subjects:
Library exhibits.; Libraries--New York (State)--Special collections.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to permission of the office of origin.
CONTAINER LIST
- Guest Book (Box 1)
- Circulation record slips: books and manuscripts, July 1992-February 1993 (Box 2)
- Circulation record slips: books and manuscripts, March 1993-May 1993 (Box 2a)
- Circulation record slips: books and manuscripts, June 1992-September 1993, books (Box 2b)
- Circulation record slips: books, July 1992-June 1993 (Box 2c)
- Circulation record slips: July 1992- September 1993, mss. (Box 3)
- Icelandic Cards (Box 4)
- Strategic Plan Records (Box 5)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. September 1993-February 1994; books pre September 1993 (Box 6)
- Book Order Receipts, 1991-2004; donor fund records, 1987-1994 (Box 7)
- Circulation record slips: books October-December 1993; mss. December 1993; books and mss. January-April 1994 (Box 8)
- Chron File January-December 1992 (Box 9)
- MOD imaging disks (Cornell); imaging disks (Johnson Family and Anti-Slavery) (Box 10)
- Digital Tape Backup (Box 11)
- Division address book and room reservation schedule book; RBMS subject files and drawings of Kroch exhibit cases (Box 12)
- Printer's master copy of the guide (Box 13)
- Chron files from January 1993-December 1994 (Box 14)
- Chron files from January 1995-May 1996 (Box 15)
- Registration Cards 1992-1993 A-M (Box 16)
- Registration Cards 1992-1993 N-Z (Box 17)
- 1993-1994 A-Z (Box 17)
- Public service meetings-August 1995 (Box 17)
- Book reserves (fall, spring, summer 1995 (Box 17)
- Spring 1991-1992, 1994, 1995) (Box 17)
- NEH seminar (Box 17)
- Statistics (1993-1994, 1995-1996) (Box 17)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. April-September 1994 (Box 18)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. September-December 1994 (Box 19)
- Circulation record slips: books January-August 1994 (Box 20)
- Circulation record slips: books September-December 1994; mss. Feburary-June 1994 (Box 21)
- Circulation record slips: mss. July-December 1994; books and mss. January-March 1995 (Box 22)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. March-July 1995 (Box 23)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. July-October 1995 (Box 24)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. November-December 1995; books January-April 1995 (Box 25)
- Files: BERO-BL and C-CAR, 1990-1991 (Box 26)
- Files: A-Z, 1992-1993 (Box 26)
- Files: A-CL, 1993-1994 (Box 26)
- Files: A-CL, 1993-1994 (Box 27)
- Files: A-P, 1994-1995 (Box 28)
- Files: Q-Z, 1994-1995 (Box 29)
- Files: A-G, 1995-1996 (Box 29)
- Files: H-Z, 1995-1996 (several folders that contain letters with no dates) (Box 30)
- Policies and Procedures RMC 1993 (Box 31)
- Reference Manual for Reference Desk (Box 31)
- Public Service Forms and Procedures 1992-1994 (Box 31)
- Public Service Meeting RMC 1994 (Box 31)
- Hygrothermograph Charts (Box 31)
- Circulation record slips: books April-November 1995 (Box 32)
- Circulation record slips: books November-December 1995; mss. January-October 1995 (Box 33)
- Circulation record slips: mss. November-December 1995; books and mss. January-April 1996 (Box 34)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. May-July 1996 (Box 35)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. August-December 1996 (Box 36)
- Circulation record slips: books January-June 1996 (Box 37)
- Circulation record slips: books July-December 1996 (Box 38)
- Circulation record slips: mss. January-December 1996 (Box 39)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. January-April 1997 (Box 40)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. May-July 1997 (Box 41)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. August-November 1997 (Box 42)
- Registration cards 1994-1995 A-ROGERS (Box 43)
- Registration cards 1994-1995 ROL-Z (Box 44)
- Registration cards 1995-1996 A-L (Box 45)
- Registration cards 1995-1996 M-Z (Box 46)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. December 1997; books January-June 1997 (Box 47)
- Circulation record slips: books July-December 1997 (Box 48)
- Circulation record slips: mss. January-September 1997 (Box 49)
- Circulation record slips: mss. October-December 1997; books and mss. January-March 1998 (Box 50)
- Reference Letters 1993-1995 (Box 51)
- Reference Letters: Alphabetical A-L 1996-1997 (Box 51)
- Reference Letters: Alphabetical M-Z 1996-1997 (Box 52)
- Reference Letters: Alphabetical A-Z 1997-1998 (Box 53)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. 4-7, 1998 (Box 54)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. 8-11, 1998 (Box 55)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. November-December 1998; books 1-5, 1998 (Box 56)
- Electronic records files including records compiled by Cheryl Stadel-Bevans, 1998-1999 for an 18-month NHPRC (National Historical Publications and Records Commission)-sponsored project to investigate the requirements for electronic administrative records at Cornell, and a report by Nancy McGovern on electronic student records systems (Box 57)
- Chron and Reference letters, July 1999-June 2000 (Box 58)
- Margaret Nichols: Division cataloging files; Phil McCray: GTO/ barcoding files; Margaret Nichols files, 1994-2003 (Box 59)
- Stringfellow and Berrigan administrative files and correspondence (Box 60)
- Chron files, June 1996-March 1997 (Box 61)
- Chron files, April 1997-June 1998 (Box 62)
- Chron files, July 1998-June 1999 (Box 63)
- RMC Reference correspondence: A-Z, 1998-1999 (Box 64)
- RMC public services files, 1992-1994 (Box 64)
- Student Projects (Box 64)
- SCRLC teams workshop, 1995 (Box 64)
- shelving committee (Box 64)
- shelving in new building (Box 64)
- billing, 1995 (Box 64)
- Electronic book (Box 65)
- Dead Numbers File: Transfers to Rare (published materials to be cataloged in Rare): accession files, other documentation of transfers in collection number order (Box 66-68)
- Transfers to other collections in RMC (Box 66-68)
- Deaccessions: accession files, other documentation of deaccessions in collection number order (Box 66-68)
- Untitled material (Box 69)
- RMC General Correspondence, 1989-1997: La - Z (Box 70)
- Margaret Nichols files (Box 71)
  Cataloging projects, cataloging information, technical services information, public services miscellany, food exhibit [2002]
- Circulation record slips: books June-December 1998; mss. January-February 1998 (Box 72)
- Circulation record slips: mss. 3-10/98 (Box 73)
- Circulation record slips: mss. 12/98; books and mss. 1-4/99 (Box 74)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. 4-8/99 (Box 75)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. 9-12/99 (Box 76)
- Circulation record slips: books 1-9/99 (Box 77)
- Circulation record slips: books 10-12/99; mss. 1-6/99 (Box 78)
- Circulation record slips: mss. 7-12/99; books and mss. 1-2/00 (Box 79)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. 3-5/00 (Box 80)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. 6-9/00 (Box 81)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. 10-12/00; books 1-4/00 (Box 82)
- Circulation record slips: books 4-12/00; mss. 1-2/00 (Box 83)
- Circulation record slips: mss. 3-11/00 (Box 84)
- Circulation record slips: mss. 12/00; books and mss. 1-3/01 (Box 85)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. 4-8/01 (Box 86)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. 8-11/01 (Box 87)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. 12/01; books 1-8/01 (Box 88)
- Circulation record slips: books 9-12/01; mss. 1-4/01 (Box 89)
- Circulation record slips: mss. 5-12/01; books and mss. 1/02 (Box 90)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. 2-5/02 (Box 91)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. 6-9/02 (Box 92)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. 10-12/02; Books 1/02 (Box 93)
- Circulation record slips: books 2-10/2002 (Box 94)
- Circulation record slips: books 11-12/2002; mss. 1-7/2002 (Box 95)
- Circulation record slips: mss. 8-12/2002; books and mss. 1-2/2003 (Box 96)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. 3-5/2003 (Box 97)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. 6-[8/2003] (Box 98)
- Class reserve cards (Box 99)
- Circulation record slips: APC's paged 1997-2002 (white and yellow copies) (Box 100)
- Registration card statistics 1996/1997 - 2000/2001 compiled by Boris Michev (Box 101)
- Tech processing - Division Manuals (Box 102)
- Cataloging - 590 display (Box 102)
- Cataloging - special files (Box 102)
- Tech Processing - preservation photocopies (Box 102)
- Tech processing - size designations (Box 102)
- Public services - policy documents (Box 102)
- RMC Web redesign (Box 102)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. [9-11/2003] (Box 103)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. [12/2003]; books 1-8/2003 (Box 104)
- Circulation record slips: books 9-12/2003, mss. 1-5/2003 (Box 105)
- Circulation record slips: mss. 6-12/2003 (Box 106)
- 7/1/2002-6/30/2003: Chron files, donor correspondence (Box 107)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. 1-3/2004 (Box 108)
- Margaret Nichols' office files (Box 109)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. 4-6 (G)/2004 (Box 110)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. 6(H)-8/2004 (Box 111)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. 9-11/2004 (Box 112)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. 12/2004; books 1-5/2004 (Box 113)
- Circulation record slips: books 6-10/2004 (Box 114)
- Circulation record slips: books 11-12/2004; mss. 1-4/2004 (Box 115)
- Circulation record slips: mss. 5-9/2004 (Box 116)
- Nolen Fund administrative records (Box 117)
- Grant proposals, 1998-1999 (Box 118, Folder 1)
- Planning materials, 1996 (Box 118, Folder 2)
- Reference/permissions - Maggie Hale, 1995-1996 (Box 118, Folder 3)
- HSX subscriptions/memberships 1991-1994 (Box 118, Folder 4)
- Icelandic Symposium, LC, 2000 (Box 118, Folder 5)
- Icelandic Steering Committee Material, 2000 (Box 118, Folder 6)
- Safety Steering Committee (Box 118, Folder 7)
- RMC Strategic Plan, 1993-1994 (Box 118, Folder 8)
- Chron File, July 2001 (Box 119, Folder 1)
- Chron File, August 2001 (Box 119, Folder 2)
- Chron File, September 2001 (Box 119, Folder 3)
- Chron File, October 2001 (Box 119, Folder 4)
- Chron File, November 2001 (Box 119, Folder 5)
- Chron File, December 2001 (Box 119, Folder 6)
- Chron File, January 2002 (Box 119, Folder 7)
- Chron File, February 2002 (Box 119, Folder 8)
- Chron File, March 2002 (Box 119, Folder 9)
- Chron File, April 2002 (Box 119, Folder 10)
- Chron File, May 2002 (Box 119, Folder 11)
- Chron File, June 2002 (Box 119, Folder 12)
- Permission letters, 1994-2001 (Box 120)
- Alpha File - A-Z, July 2001-July 2002 (Box 121)
- Circulation record slips: mss.10-12/2004; books and mss. 1/2005 (Box 122)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. 2-8/2005 (Box 123)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. 9-12/2005 (Box 124)
- Circulation record slips: books 1-6/2005 (Box 125)
- Circulation record slips: books 7-12/2005 (Box 126)
- Circulation record slips: mss. 1-6/2005 (Box 127)
- Circulation record slips: Mss. 7-10/2005 (Box 128)
- Circulation record slips: mss. 10-12/2005; books and mss. 1-3(H)/2006 (Box 129)
- Grant proposals and additional budget and background information from the 1990's for the: (Box 130)
  - French Revolution Collection-retrospective conversion and preservation
  - Icelandic Collection
- Margaret Nichols Files: Library staff training and professional development documents: 1993-2001 (Box 131)
- Circulation reports (Annex): December 1997 - December 2001 (Box 132)
- Circulation reports (Annex): 1987-2001 (Box 133)
- Chron Files for July 2002-September 2003 (Box 134)
- Chron Files: October 2003-June 2004 (Box 135)
- Ref Files: 2002-2003 - A-J (Box 135)
- Chron Files: October 2003-June 2004 (Box 136)
- Ref Files: 2002-2003 - K-Z (Box 136)
- Chron Files: October 2003-June 2004 (Box 137)
- Ref Files:2003-2004 - A-Z (Box 137)
- Circulation record slips: books and manuscripts, 3(H)-6(APS), W. Wawro project/2006 (Box 138)
- Circulation record slips: books and manuscripts, 6-8/2006 (Box 139)
- Circulation record slips: books and manuscripts, 9-11(P)/2006 (Box 140)
- Circulation record slips: books and manuscripts, 11(Q)-12/2006; books 1-6/2006 (Box 141)
- Circulation record slips: books, 7-12/2006; manuscripts, 1-3/2006 (Box 142)
- Circulation record slips: manuscripts, 4-10/2006 (Box 143)
- Circulation record slips: manuscripts, 11-12/2006; books and manuscripts,1-3(H)/2007 (Box 144)
- Circulation record slips: books and manuscripts, 3(I)-6(H)/2007 (Box 145)
- Circulation record slips: books and manuscripts, 6(I)-8/2007 (Box 146)
- Chron Files: June 2004-April 2005 (Box 147)
- Reference Files: 2004-2005 A-T (Box 148)
- Reference Files: 2004-2005 U-Z (Box 149)
- Reference letters: June 2005 (Box 149)
- Rare files: HSX donor correspondence, 1997-2003 (Box 150)
- Rare files: HSX files, 1997-2003 (Box 150)
- Rare files: RMC book fund reports, 1992/1993-1999/2000 (Box 151)
- Rare files: Gift Book lists (Box 152)
- Rare files: Desiderata lists, 1992-2005 (Box 152)
- Plaque containing clipping re opening of Kroch Library (Box 153)
- Katherine Reagan files (Box 154)
- Dante/Petrarch project request slips: returns (Box 155-156)
- Dante/Petrarch project request slips: not returned (Box 156)
- Inventory miscellany, 2001 (Box 157)
- Inventory miscellany, 2004 (Box 158)
- Circulation record slips: books and manuscripts, 9-11(J)2007 (Box 159)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. 11(K)-12/2007; books, 1-4/2007 (Box 160)
- Circulation record slips: books, 5-11/2007 (Box 161)
- Circulation record slips: books, 12/2007; manuscripts, 1-6/2007 (Box 162)
- Circulation record slips: manuscripts, 7-12/2007; books and manuscripts, 1/2008 (Box 163)
- Circulation record slips: books and manuscripts, 2-4/2008 (Box 164)
- Circulation record slips: books and manuscripts, 5-8 (G)/2008 (Box 165)
- Circulation record slips: books and manuscripts, 8(H)-11 (H)/2008 (Box 166)
- Circulation record slips: books and manuscripts, 11(I)-12(H)/2008 (Box 167)
- Annex request slips (Box 168)
- Margaret Nichols files (Box 169)
- ILS returns, July 1, 2001 (Box 170)
- ILS returns, 2002 (Box 170)
- Rare manuscripts list (Box 170)
- Bibliographic memory aids (Box 170)
- Rebecca Davidson files (Box 170)
- Cataloging and classification issues re images and image data bases (Box 170)
- Categories for Descriptions of Works of Art (Getty) (Box 170)
- Image Database Projects (Box 170)
- Product and other general information: Apple New Media seminar, 3/27/96; OpenDoc; Cumulus; EmBark; Brittanica Electronic Products; FileMaker, Imformix/Illustra; Optix, Re:discovery; Willoughby (Box 170)
- A. B. Mullett architectural designs (Box 170)
- McCarthy project files (Box 170)
- Noni Korf Vidal files (Box 170)
- RMC Logo development (Box 170)
- OPAC Endeavor (Box 170)
- Docs - Josh Labouve, 12/29/03 (Box 170)
- Print materials (Box 170)
- RMC greeting cards (Box 170)
- Public Service (Box 170)
- IMAG - CU (Box 170)
- Web Projects: Mozart, Claire Holt (Box 170)
- Web Projects: Claire Holt (Box 170)
- Web Projects: Howell photographs (Box 170)
- Web Projects: ADA compliant with design, misc. (Box 170)
- LUNA/SUN (Box 170)
- Hill: plates, photos (Box 170)
- Home Economics/Human Ecology Site (Box 170)
- Software (Box 170)
- Student employment (Box 170)
- Home Ec photo collection demo (Box 170)
- Photo Shop (Box 170)
- Buildings (Box 170)
- APC (Box 170)
- RMC Films (Box 170)
- Photo Science 4/3/2882 (Box 170)
- Visual Services 4/3/1885 (Box 170)
- News Service (Box 170)
- Media Services 21/37/2227 (Box 170)
- All (Univ.) Photo Collections (Box 170)
- Aggregated Cornell Photographs 13/6/2957 (Box 170)
- University Photography 4/14/2883 (Box 170)
- Suzy Szasz Palmer files (Box 171)
- Reunion 2000 (Box 171)
- Reunion 2001 (Box 171)
- CU-LIB Listserve (Box 171)
- E-book Working Group (Box 171)
- Greatest Hits (Box 171)
- Tours (Box 171)
- RMC outreach program (Box 171)
- RMC publications (Box 171)
- Oliver Sacks (Box 171)
- Cultural Events Committee (Box 171)
- Toni Morrison visit, 10/2-6/00 (Box 171)
- Photocopying and photographing materials (Box 171)
- Campus store (Box 171)
- LUNA (Box 171)
- Loans (Box 171)
- Ivory-billed woodpecker (Box 171)
- Hirshland Gallery (Box 171)
- RMC handout (Box 171)
- Asian American Studies 480 (Box 171)
- E. B. White (Box 171)
- Children's literature (Box 171)
- AP American History/Trumansburg (Box 171)
- Law Class, Summer 2001, Lucy Gold (Box 171)
- Anthropology 301/AMS 307, 3/14/2002 (Box 171)
- Aviation and Aeronautics (Box 171)
- Classes 1999-2000 descriptions, etc. (Box 171)
- Cell Biology - Randy Wayne, 10/28/2002 (Box 171)
- Classes (requests, etc.) 2000/2001 (Box 171)
- History 100.31, Tues. 9/25/(12:35-12:55 only) (Box 171)
- History 418 (Box 171)
- History 459/659: Radicals and Revolutionaries in modern Latin America, 9/19/R. Craib (Box 171)
- Medieval Studies 101: Understanding the human mind, 9/30, B. Goehring (Box 171)
- Medieval Studies 101.4 (Box 171)
- Philosophy 100, Tues. 1/29 (Box 171)
- Medical Philosophical Literature (AOS), 9/7/2001 (Box 171)
- Philosophy/Women's Studies: 17th Century Women philosophy (Box 171)
- Rural Sociology 101 (introduction) (Box 171)
- Schurman "tour," 11/19/2001; Unidentified tour/class (Box 171)
- Ithaca College - Law/SCT, M. Miller, Thursday 2/7, 9:00-10:30 (Box 171)
- STS 105: Bodies and Science, September 18, 2002, Aryn Martin (Box 171)
- STS 631, Wednesday 2/20, 2:30-4:25 (Box 171)
- Marathon 8th graders: Civil War, 10/29 (cancelled) (Box 171)
- Belle Sherman, Thursday 1/31 (Box 171)
- Camp Cornell (Box 171)
- History of Art - Slide Library materials - Notes from C.L./Lisa, etc. (one letter size folder, one legal size folder (Box 171)
- Margaret Nichols files (Box 172)
- V-806: Masterpiece Theatre opening and credits 1993, V-816: Kroch Library excavation and initial construction (summer 1992) (Box 173)
- Files relating to Media Services Archives jobs, APC Visual Services, Photo Services (Box 174)
- Reference letters: A-L, 2005-2006 (Box 175)
- Reference letters: N-Z, 2005-2006 (Box 176)
- American Indian Heritage Month at Cornell, 11/2005 (poster) (Box 177)
- Kari Smith files: sources bibliography (draft) (Box 178)
- Kari Smith files: Stevens Family Papers (Box 178)
- Kari Smith files: Cooper Bridge (Box 178)
- Kari Smith files: McCarthy book (Box 178)
- Kari Smith files: LaFayette Web site (Box 178)
- Kari Smith files: McCarthy Web site (Box 178)
- Kari Smith files: Euclid meeting (Box 178)
- Kari Smith files: LUNA (Box 178)
- Kari Smith files: Diver photographs (Box 178)
- Kari Smith files: Eastern Wine & Grape (Box 178)
- Photocopy orders, July 2005-June 2007 (Box 179)
- Reproduction orders, August 2005-June 2007 (Box 180)
- Reference letters: A - J, 2007 (Box 181)
- Reference letters: K - Sm, 2007 (Box 182)
- Reference letters: So-Z, 2007 (Box 183)
- Reference letters: May 1 - August 31, 2007 (Box 183)
- (Box 184)
- Circulation record slips: books and manuscripts, 11 (I)-12/2008; books, 1-4/2008 (Box 185)
- Circulation record slips: books, 5-12/2008; manuscripts, 1-2/2008 (Box 186)
- Circulation record slips: manuscripts, 3-10/2008 (Box 187)
- Circulation record slips: manuscripts, 11-12/2008; books and manuscripts, 1-4 (E)/2009 (Box 188)
- Circulation record slips: books and manuscripts, 4 (F)-7 (L)/2009 (Box 189)
- Circulation record slips: books and manuscripts, 7 (M)-10/2009 (Box 190)
- Circulation record slips: books and manuscripts, 11-12-/2009; books 1-4/2009 (Box 191)
- Circulation record slips: books, 5-12/2009 (Box 192)
- Chron File, July 2005 - June 2007 (Box 193)
- Circulation record slips: manuscripts, 1-7/2009 (Box 194)
- David Block Native American files (Box 195)
- Nancy Dean files: 1991-1992 Annual Report (Box 196)
- Nancy Dean files: Coverlet from Mrs. Pharness (given to costume collection) (Box 196)
- Nancy Dean files: Coll. of Architecture Project corresp. (Box 196)
- Nancy Dean files: former collections transferred to ARP (Box 196)
- Nancy Dean files: Archives Pamphlet Collection (Box 196)
- Nancy Dean files: Survey of Archives printed material (Box 196)
- Nancy Dean files: E. Cornell Civil War letters (Box 196)
- Nancy Dean files: Black students (Box 196)
- Nancy Dean files: Myron Taylor organ rolls (Box 196)
- Nancy Dean files: 1976 Presidential exhibit (Box 196)
- Nancy Dean files: J. Brumberg (Box 196)
- Nancy Dean files: sample stock certificates (Box 196)
- Nancy Dean files: Colt guns (Box 196)
- Nancy Dean files: "Election Year Argument Settled" (Box 196)
- Nancy Dean files: political slides (Box 196)
- Nancy Dean files: newspapers (Box 196)
- Nancy Dean files: clippings (Box 196)
- Nancy Dean files: Trumansburg newspapers (Box 196)
- Mezzanine sign for elevator (Box 196)
- Vault card (Box 196)
- Nancy Dean files:Dragon Day, St. Patricks Day clippings (Box 196)
- Nancy Dean files: Cornell Pumpkin clippings (Box 196)
- Nancy Dean files: AA@CU (Box 196)
- Nancy Dean files: genealogy: A. D. White family, Ezra Cornell family, Blair family, Barnard family, Wood family, McGraw-Fiske families (Box 197)
- Eastern Wine and Grape Project records (Box 197)
- Circulation record slips: mss 8-12/2009, books and mss. 1-2/2010 (Box 198)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. 3-6 (L)/2010 (Box 199)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. 6 (M)-9 (L)/2010 (Box 200)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. 9 (M)-12/2010; books 1-2/2010 (Box 201)
- Circulation record slips: books 1-10/2010 (Box 202)
- Circulation record slips: books 11-12/2010; mss. 1-6/2010 (Box 203)
- Circulation record slips: mss. 7-12/2010 (Box 204)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. 1- /2011 (Box 205)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. - /2011 (Box 206)
- Circulation record slips: books and mss. - /2011 (Box 207)
- Circulation record slips: books 1- /2011 (Box 208)
- Circulation record slips: mss. 1- /2011 (Box 209)
- Circulation record slips: Annex requests, 9/07 - 12/08 (Box 210)
- Kindle electronic book reader, 2 versions (Box 211)